<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Enable Busoga</title>
    <link>https://distracted-hopper-50f30d.netlify.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Enable Busoga</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 21:30:42 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://distracted-hopper-50f30d.netlify.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Barbara Project</title>
      <link>https://distracted-hopper-50f30d.netlify.com/projects/barbara-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 21:30:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distracted-hopper-50f30d.netlify.com/projects/barbara-project/</guid>
      <description>The Barbara project was started in 2011. It came about following a visit by two health professionals from UK, Penny and Katy, who visited the parish of Bupadhengo in Busoga linked to their church &amp;lsquo;St James By the Park Church in Southampton&amp;rsquo;.
They named the project &amp;lsquo;The Barbara Project&amp;rsquo; in loving memory of Katy&amp;rsquo;s Sister Barbara who died in 2006 aged 50 from cancer. She had worked devotedly most of her life with children with profound physical and learning disabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Improvements</title>
      <link>https://distracted-hopper-50f30d.netlify.com/projects/school-improvements/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 21:34:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distracted-hopper-50f30d.netlify.com/projects/school-improvements/</guid>
      <description>Funds have been raised to complete building work for staff accommodation, school classrooms, school books and water sources in order to improve the standards of village schools. Funding for this work is largely carried out from UK. Construction work is usually carried out by a third party organisation The Henry Van-Straubenzie Memorial Fund (HVSMF). Occasional visits are made to schools in Busoga by visitors from the UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Business Development</title>
      <link>https://distracted-hopper-50f30d.netlify.com/projects/small-business-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 21:35:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://distracted-hopper-50f30d.netlify.com/projects/small-business-development/</guid>
      <description>Investment from the UK has been made into businesses: growing and drying local fruit; growing and planting tree seedlings and charging mobile phones from solar panels.
Dried Fruit The drying of locally harvested fruits such as pineapple and mango uses the power of the sun of which there is an abundance.
Each set of driers supports a number of families who can bring their fruit to be processed. Once dried the fruit is bagged and sold locally to schools and other educational establishments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>